Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Communications Department Records, 1963-2004; 28115
  - Subseries IV:B: Bill Schleicher Records, 1992-2004., 28146
    - Political Action, 2003-2004; cuid5324; 28156 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Bush v. Kerry), 2004; cuid5325; 28155 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases, 2003-2004; cuid5326; 28154 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Rallies: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5327; 28153 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Reagan, Ronald: Death of, 2004; cuid5328; 28152 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Republican National Convention Protests, 2004; cuid5329; 28151 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Roberts, Lillian: Re-Election of, 2004; cuid5330; 28150 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Shop Stewards: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5331; 28149 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Staff: Meeting Notes, 2003; cuid5332; 28148 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Telephone Directory, 1997; cuid5333; 28147 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Subseries IV:C: Public Employee Press Research Files, 1963-1993., 28116
    - Anti-Ballistic Missile System (ABM), 1969; cuid5334; 28145 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Blue Collar Locals: Citywide Strike, 1971; cuid5335; 28144 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: State Civil Service Eployees Association (CSEA) Strike, 1972; cuid5336; 307919 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: General, undated; 1963; 1970-1995; cuid5337; 307920 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Education Conference, 1963, 1985; cuid5338; 28143 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Event Programs and Announcements, undated, 1973-1978, 1992-1993; cuid5339; 28142 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1967-1968; cuid5340; 28141 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Exposé, 1971-1972; cuid5341; 28140 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Hospital Exposé: Bellevue Hospital, 1965-1971; cuid5342; 28139 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Exposé: Kings County Hospital, 1967-1972; cuid5343; 28138 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Hospital Exposé: Lincoln Hospital, 1966-1972; cuid5344; 28137 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Interview Notes: Members of Locals 372, 376, 384, 1113, 1407, 1501, 1502, 1549, 1597, and 2021, undated; cuid5345; 28136 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Leadership Conference, 1981; cuid5346; 28135 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1973-1980; cuid5347; 28134 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Education Conferences, 1982, 1987, 1989; cuid5348; 28133 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973; cuid5349; 28132 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976; cuid5350; 28131 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Nurse's Aides Upgrading Program, 1966-1970; cuid5351; 28130 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Local 983 (Motor Vehicle Operators): Service Awards, 1975; cuid5352; 28129 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Local 1087 (Prevailing Rate Employees): Radio Repair Mechanics, 1978; cuid5353; 28128 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Local 1795 (Stationary Firemen): Safety Issues, 1970-1976, 1982, 1992; cuid5354; 28127 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1967-1972; cuid5355; 28126 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals I, 1967-1968, 1972; cuid5356; 28125 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals II, 1967-1968, 1972; cuid5357; 28124 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Notes, undated; cuid5358; 28123 (Box 43a, Folder 1)
    - Paycheck Cashing: Joseph Sperling v. Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company, 1976; cuid5359; 28122 (Box 43a, Folder 2)
    - Political Action: Goldberg-Paterson Campaign (Opposition to AFL-CIO Rockefeller Endorsement), 1970; cuid5360; 28121 (Box 43a, Folder 3)
    - Safety Committee Inspections, 1975-1976; cuid5361; 28120 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Substance Abuse Conference, 1984; cuid5362; 28119 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Taylor Law: Madison Square Garden Rally, 1967; cuid5363; 28118 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Taylor Law: Response to Sanitation and Teachers' Strikes, 1967-1968; cuid5364; 28117 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000; 27581
  - Agreement: DC 37 and AFSCME, 1956; cuid5365; 28114 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Agreement: New York State Federation of Labor and New York State Industrial Union Council, 1958; cuid5366; 28113 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO: Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing Manual, undated; cuid5367; 28112 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME: Affiliation Agreement with Lassen County Employees Association, undated; cuid5368; 28111 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME: Employees' Pension Plan, undated; cuid5369; 28110 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME: Financial Statements, 1996-1997; cuid5370; 28109 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME: Secretary-Treasurer Educational Workshop, undated; cuid5371; 28108 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME: Trust Agreement with National Bank of Washington, 1975; cuid5372; 28107 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAE), Local 1707, 1958-1963; cuid5373; 28106 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707, 1964-1967; cuid5374; 28105 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME, CSAE, Local 1707: Contested Election of Delegates to AFSCME Convention, 1964; cuid5375; 28104 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME, Council 50, 1967-1969; cuid5376; 28103 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME, Council 50: Mental Hospital Strike-- Clippings, 1968; cuid5377; 28102 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME, Council 62, 1998; cuid5378; 28101 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME Employees Federal Credit Union, 1972-1973; cuid5379; 28100 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th), 1958; cuid5380; 28099 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th): Correspondence, 1957-1958; cuid5381; 28097 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME International Convention (11th) (Oversize), 1958; cuid5382; 28098 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME International Convention (16th), 1966; cuid5383; 28096 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Agendas, 1998; cuid5384; 28095 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1968, 1975; cuid5385; 28094 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Minutes, 1997-1998; cuid5386; 28093 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files, 1968; cuid5387; 28092 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files I, 1975; cuid5388; 28091 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files II, 1975; cuid5389; 28090 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - AFSCME International Executive Board: Reports and Background Files III, 1975; cuid5390; 28089 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - AFSCME Legislation Department, 1997-1998; cuid5391; 28088 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - AFSCME Task Force for the Future, 1998; cuid5392; 28087 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Benefit Fund, 1958-1965; cuid5393; 28086 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Blue Collar Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972; cuid5394; 28085 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Chaplains Organizing Committee, 1982; cuid5395; 28084 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Employees, 1972, 1976; cuid5396; 28083 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Citywide Contract, 1967, 1970-1976, 1985; cuid5397; 28082 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Clerical Division: Citywide Organizing Materials, 1966; cuid5398; 28081 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Clerical-Administrative Division: Leaflets, 1970-1972; cuid5399; 28080 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Clippings: General, 1967-1987, 1991-1998, 2008; cuid5400; 28079 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining: Citywide Agreement Impasse, 1981-1982; cuid5401; 28078 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Union Responsibility (COUR), 1961, 1963-1964; cuid5402; 28077 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Community School Board, District 1 Elections, 1974-1975; cuid5403; 28076 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: General, 1955-1956; cuid5404; 28075 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: General, 1957-1958; cuid5405; 28074 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1959-Jun 1959; cuid5406; 28073 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1959-Dec 1959; cuid5407; 28072 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: General, Jan 1960-Jun 1960; cuid5408; 28071 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: General, Jul 1960-1962; 1968-1977; 1986; cuid5409; 28070 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Delegate Calculations, 1982; cuid5410; 28069 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 Charter, 1978-1979; cuid5411; 28068 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - DC 37: General/History, 1944-1945, 1965-1972, 1982; cuid5412; 28067 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Education Fund, 1970-1976; cuid5413; 28066 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Education Fund, undated, 1982; cuid5414; 28065 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fiscal Crisis, 1970, 1974-1976; cuid5415; 28064 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Forms: General, 1970s; cuid5416; 28063 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Grievance Procedures and Collective Bargaining Manual, 1963; cuid5417; 28062 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Health and Security Plan, 1970-1976, 1988; cuid5418; 28061 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1996-Sep 1996; cuid5419; 28060 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Health News Daily, Sep 1996-Dec 1996; cuid5420; 28059 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Health News Daily, Dec 1996-Feb 1997; cuid5421; 28058 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Health News Daily, Feb 1997-Apr 1997; cuid5422; 28057 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Health News Daily, Apr 1997-Jun 1997; cuid5423; 28056 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Health News Daily, Jun 1997-Jul 1997; cuid5424; 28055 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1966; cuid5425; 28054 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1967; cuid5426; 28053 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1968; cuid5427; 28052 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Hospitals: Clippings, 1976; cuid5428; 28051 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Hospitals--Strikes: Clippings, 1968; cuid5429; 28050 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Hospitals Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971; cuid5430; 28049 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Housing Division: Organizing Materials, 1966; cuid5431; 28048 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Irish Heritage, 1975; cuid5432; 28047 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Leaflets: General, 1962-1966; 1970-1976; 1981; cuid5433; 28046 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Leaflets: Other Organizations, 1967-1968; 1993; cuid5434; 28045 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1964, 1971-1976; cuid5435; 28044 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Leaflets: Social and Political Issues, 1982; 1987; cuid5436; 28043 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Legislation (Public Health), 1971; cuid5437; 28042 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Local 135B (Brooklyn Museum) and 135M (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1956; cuid5438; 28041 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks), 1955-1966; cuid5439; 28040 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Grievances, 1956-1965; cuid5440; 28039 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Local 149 (Department of Parks): Meeting Notices, 1958-1966; cuid5441; 28038 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Local 154 (NYC Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1963-1966, 1972-1974, ca.1982; cuid5442; 28037 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Local 188 (Municipal Examiners and Analysts), 1967; cuid5443; 28036 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1953-1959; cuid5444; 28035 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1960-1963; cuid5445; 28034 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), 1964-1967; cuid5446; 28033 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees), undated, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5447; 28032 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Assistant Supervisors of Recreation (Oversize), 1963; cuid5448; 28031 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Baron v. Morris Case, 1963; cuid5449; 28030 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Grievances, 1956-1966; cuid5450; 28029 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Jimmy Carosella, 1990-1993; cuid5451; 28028 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Meeting Notices and Printed Material, 1965-1966; cuid5452; 28027 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Local 299 (Recreation Employees): Newsletters, 1965-1966; cuid5453; 28026 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Local 322 (Uniformed Sanitation Men), 1960-1961; cuid5454; 28025 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Local 371 (Social Service Employees Union, SSEU), 1958-1962; cuid5455; 28024 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1963-1964; cuid5456; 28023 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5457; 28022 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1965-Dec 1965; cuid5458; 28021 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jan 1966-Jun 1966; cuid5459; 28020 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), Jul 1966-Dec 1966; cuid5460; 28019 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Local 371 (SSEU), 1967, 1973, 1980-1982; cuid5461; 28018 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Certification Amendment, 1998; cuid5462; 28017 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Children's Shelters, 1970; cuid5463; 28016 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Collective Bargaining, 1964; cuid5464; 28015 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Constitution and Bylaws, undated, 1961-1964; cuid5465; 28014 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1956-1961; cuid5466; 28013 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Grievances, 1963-1967; cuid5467; 28012 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Manual of Operations and Forms, 1957; cuid5468; 28011 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5469; 28010 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Jul 1965-Apr 1967; cuid5470; 28009 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Minutes, 1965-1966; cuid5471; 28008 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Newsletters and Bulletins, 1963-1969; 1984; cuid5472; 28007 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Printed Material, 1962-1966, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5473; 28006 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1962-1966; cuid5474; 28005 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Election and Strike, 1964-1967; cuid5475; 28004 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): SSEU Printed Material, 1963-1966; cuid5476; 28003 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Budget Crisis, 1962; cuid5477; 28002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike I, 1964-1966; cuid5478; 28001 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike II, 1964-1966; cuid5479; 28000 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike (Oversize), 1965; cuid5480; 27999 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Bulletins, 1965; cuid5481; 27998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Captain Reports, 1965; cuid5482; 27997 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Local 371 (SSEU): Welfare Strike Report, 1967; cuid5483; 27996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Agreements, 1974-1976; 1980-1982; cuid5484; 27995 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Constitution, undated; cuid5485; 27994 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Family Paraprofessionals, 1973; cuid5486; 27993 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, 1957-1963, 1973; cuid5487; 27992 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Grievances, 1957-1965; cuid5488; 27991 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): High School Program, Meeting Notices, 1961-1963; cuid5489; 27990 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1962; cuid5490; 27989 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963; cuid5491; 27988 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5492; 27987 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Minutes, 1963-1966, 1976; cuid5493; 27986 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Newsletters, 1965-1966, 1978; cuid5494; 27985 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, 1956-1966; cuid5495; 27984 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Policy Consultation Council, Minutes, 1957-1965; cuid5496; 27983 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1970-1974; cuid5497; 27982 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): Printed Material, 1975-1977; 1981-1982; 1988; cuid5498; 27981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, 1963-1966, 1971-1973; cuid5499; 27980 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Grievances, 1964-1966; 1975; 1980; cuid5500; 27979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1965-1966; cuid5501; 27978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Aides, UFT Challenge, 1973; cuid5502; 27977 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1958-1961; cuid5503; 27976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1962-1963; cuid5504; 27975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1964; cuid5505; 27974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jan 1965-Jun 1965; cuid5506; 27973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Jul 1965-Dec 1965; cuid5507; 27972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, 1966, 1973-1980; cuid5508; 27971 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1957-1961; cuid5509; 27970 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1962; cuid5510; 27969 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Grievances, 1963-1966, 1978-1979; cuid5511; 27968 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Employees, Salary Appeal Briefs, 1958-1962; cuid5512; 27967 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Local 372 (Board of Education): School Lunch Program Assistants, 1960-1962; cuid5513; 27966 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1961-1965, 1976; cuid5514; 27965 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Agreements, 1958-1965; cuid5515; 27964 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1956-Apr 1959; cuid5516; 27963 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, May 1959-1960; cuid5517; 27962 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Botanical Gardens, 1961-1965; cuid5518; 27961 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Grievances, 1958-1965; cuid5519; 27960 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1961-1966; cuid5520; 27959 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, 1957-1966, 1971; cuid5521; 27958 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Job Descriptions, 1961-1965; cuid5522; 27957 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff Committee Minutes, 1961-1963; cuid5523; 27956 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): New York Public Library, Staff News, 1960-1964; cuid5524; 27955 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1966; cuid5525; 27954 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Local 375 (Civil Service Technical Guild, CSTG), 1957-1958; cuid5526; 27953 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1959-1961; cuid5527; 27952 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1962-1963; cuid5528; 27951 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1964; cuid5529; 27950 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1965-1967, 1976; cuid5530; 27949 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Local 375 (CSTG), 1982, 1998; cuid5531; 27948 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 3, Department of Hospitals, undated, 1963-1967, 1981-1982; cuid5532; 27947 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 10, Department of Health, 1964-1967; cuid5533; 27946 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 13, Board of Water Supply, 1965-1967; cuid5534; 27945 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 14, Board of Education, 1963-1967; cuid5535; 27944 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 17, Department of Buildings, 1965-1966; cuid5536; 27943 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Chapter 38, Housing and Redevelopment Board, 1966; cuid5537; 27942 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Department of Hospitals, City Civil Service Commission Public Hearing Transcript, Mar 27, 1967; cuid5538; 27941 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Fire Prevention Inspectors, 1967; cuid5539; 27940 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Grievances, 1957-1965; cuid5540; 27939 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1957-1963, 1965, 1970-1975; cuid5541; 27938 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Minutes, 1981-1982; cuid5542; 27937 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Newsletters, 1964-1976, 1982, 1989; cuid5543; 27936 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5544; 27935 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Local 375 (CSTG): Salary Appeal Briefs and Reallocations, 1957-1967; cuid5545; 27934 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Local 376 (Construction Laborers, Highway Repairers, and Watershed Maintainers), 1966-1975, 1980-1982, 1999; cuid5546; 27933 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers), 1956-1962; cuid5547; 27932 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Constitution, 1954; cuid5548; 27931 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Legislative Issues, 1953-1957; cuid5549; 27930 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Local 379 (Council of Attendance Teachers): Minutes, 1962; cuid5550; 27929 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Local 381 (Association of Laboratory Teachers), 1960-1962; cuid5551; 27928 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Local 384 (Board of Higher Education), 1966, 1972-1976, 1980-1982; cuid5552; 27927 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1955-1959 1961; cuid5553; 27926 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1962; cuid5554; 27925 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), undated, 1963-1966, 1972-1979; cuid5555; 27924 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Grievances, 1955-1964; cuid5556; 27923 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Hospital Strike, 1976; cuid5557; 27922 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Laundry Workers Organizing, 1966; cuid5558; 27921 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1955-1966; cuid5559; 27920 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Minutes, 1962-1963; cuid5560; 27919 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Newsletters, 1964-1966; cuid5561; 27918 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Practical Nurses Organizing, 1966; cuid5562; 27917 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Printed Material, 1970-1976, 1981-1984; cuid5563; 27916 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Salary Appeal Briefs, ca.1955-1962; cuid5564; 27915 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Local 436 (United Federation of Nurses), 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5565; 27914 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Local 461 (Lifeguards), 1963-1967; cuid5566; 27913 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Local 663 (New Rochelle Employees), 1965-1968; cuid5567; 27912 (Box 50, Folder 12)